reddressboutique.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy & Security – Red Dress

Your privacy is super important to us! Red Dress Boutique (“RDB”) is committed to protecting your privacy and providing you with a safe and secure online experience. This Privacy Policy applies to www.reddressboutique.com, as well as any other website owned by RDB or communication sent by RDB. It discloses the kinds of information we gather, how we may use it, and how we may share it. Please read it carefully. It may be modified periodically. Your continued use of our website signifies your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. As always, feel free to contact us at customerservice@reddressboutique.com with any questions.

## RDB Collects Personal Information

We collect personally identifiable information to fulfill your orders, tell you about new products and deals, and provide you with an amazing shopping experience. That personal information includes, but is not limited to, your name, billing and shipping addresses, an RDB user name and password, email address, phone number, and financial information. We value your trust in us and will do everything we can to safeguard your privacy and the security of your transactions.

RDB does not retain financial information, other than possibly the last four digits of your credit card number. Our payment gateway is managed by PayPal. If you enter your credit card information on our site, PayPal will process the transaction and retain a record of it. RDB keeps no record of your full credit card number. If you checkout using your personal Amazon or PayPal account, then that organization will process the transaction using financial information you have previously provided to it.

Information that you submit about yourself may be used by RDB to provide you requested services, communicate with you about RDB products, improve your online experience, or support our continuing efforts to offer you the information and services you want most. RDB does provide aggregate statistics and information about our sales, traffic patterns and related site information to third parties. We also reserve the right to share aggregate statistical data of which your personal information is a part, as well as your specific personal information sometime in the future.

In addition, RDB may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your personal information when required to do so by law, when RDB, in its sole discretion believes that you are in violation of our Terms and Conditions, or when you violate any state or federal laws, or RDB in its sole discretion deems it necessary or appropriate to protect the personal safety of other users of RDB services or to protect the rights or property of RDB.

## Email

We know you love email! And we love to tell you about new arrivals. So we send emails to notify customers about new arrivals and special events. New arrivals can happen twice a day, so we may send ten or more emails per week. You will only receive emails if you opt in to our email marketing. You may opt out at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email, or by sending a request to customerservice@reddressboutique.com. We may send you emails to confirm your order, send tracking information, or to communicate with you specifically about your order, or in response to a question either to our email, chat, or any of our social media accounts.

## Social Media

We are active on many social media sites and we love to spend time with you there. Please know that we cannot constantly monitor our social media pages and that any information that you share may be viewed by others.

## Cookies

RDB uses “cookies” to identify visitors to our website. Cookies are bits of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies can enhance your online experience by automatically saving your preferences. We use cookies because they help us to provide you a better online experience. The information we collect through the use of cookies does allow RDB to know when and for how long you logged on to the RDB website, so that we can try to understand how to better serve your needs.

## Minors

RDB is a very family friendly company. Our products and culture reflect that. But we do not direct our website or any marketing materials to minors and do not knowingly collect specific personal information on minors.

## Contact Us

We would love to hear from you! You can email us anytime at orders@shopreddress.com. You can chat with us using the chat icon at the bottom of our website. You can call us at 706-425-8707. Our offices are open Monday through Friday, from 9-5 ET. Or all of the ways!

We are located at 240 Collins Industrial Blvd, Suite A, Athens, GA 30607
